aritzia.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy | Aritzia CA

##### Privacy Policy

Last Updated: June 13, 2018.

Your privacy is important to Aritzia LP and its corporate affiliates (collectively "Aritzia"). This Policy explains how Aritzia collects, uses, discloses, and retains your information, including the use of personal information in connection with interest-based advertising.

###### Your Consent

When you provide Aritzia with your personal information, you consent to Aritzia's collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as otherwise permitted by law.

###### Personal Information

"Personal information" means information about an identifiable individual that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your mailing address, telephone number, or e-mail address.

How Aritzia Collects Your Personal Information — You may be asked to voluntarily provide your personal information to Aritzia anytime you are in contact with Aritzia, including when you purchase products or services from Aritzia through retail stores or websites. In those circumstances you can choose not to provide certain requested personal information, but then you may not be able to purchase products or services or access or use certain features of Aritzia's websites.

For example, when you purchase products or services from Aritzia (including at an Aritzia retail store, or through an Aritzia website), when you create or manage an account with Aritzia (including a user account for an Aritzia website), when you send us an e-mail, when you register or subscribe for Aritzia's newsletters or promotions, or participate in Aritzia's promotions, sweepstakes, contests, or surveys, and when you contact Aritzia Concierge, Aritzia (or its service provider) may collect a variety of your personal information, including your name, date of birth, credit card and payment information, mailing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, phone numbers, and any other personal information you voluntarily provide. In addition, Aritzia may retain your purchase history from both retail stores and Aritzia's websites.

You might also provide Aritzia with the personal information (such as name, e-mail, mailing, and shipping address) of other persons, such as family or friends for whom you purchase products or services (including gift cards) or to whom you ship purchases, or friends that you register for a refer-a-friend promotion or similar services, or friends that you share a product or article with from Aritzia's websites. Please ensure that you have the consent of other persons before you provide their personal information to Aritzia.

How Aritzia Uses Your Personal Information — Aritzia uses your personal information for various purposes in connection with our relationship with you for the provision of our products and services, including: (a) to contact and correspond with you regarding your transactions and your use of Aritzia's products and services and to provide you with Aritzia Concierge services, (b) to provide you with information regarding Aritzia's announcements, promotions, upcoming events, new products, special features, and store openings; (c) to facilitate transactions and process orders and payments for products and services purchased by you (including to remind you of un-purchased items left in your online shopping cart, to contact you regarding billing and payment discrepancies, and to validate receipts); (d) to process and respond to your specific suggestions, comments, inquiries and requests, and to otherwise administer Aritzia's relationship with you; (e) to personalize and improve your shopping experience; (f) to administer and facilitate your participation in sweepstakes, contests, and promotions; (g) to create and manage your account; and (h) to develop, deliver, and improve Aritzia's products, services and advertising.

Aritzia may also develop a confidential profile for you, which will be used to provide services to you and facilitate your transactions with Aritzia and your use of Aritzia's websites and services.

Aritzia may combine your personal information collected through various sources, including information collected at Aritzia's retail stores and through Aritzia's websites, and information obtained from other sources.

Aritzia may use personal information to create non-personal information, as defined in the next section, and Aritzia may then use, disclose, transfer, and retain the non-personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

###### Non-Personal Information

Aritzia also creates and collects "non-personal information" - information that is not associated with or linked to your personal information, including personal information that has been aggregated or otherwise anonymized so that it no longer relates to an identifiable individual.

Aritzia may use, disclose, transfer and retain non-personal information for any purpose and in any manner whatsoever.

If non-personal information is combined with personal information, then the non-personal information will be treated as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

###### Cookies and Other Technologies

Aritzia's websites, online services, e-mail messages, and advertisements may use "cookies" and other similar technologies, such as web beacons, pixel or gif tags, and action tags. Those technologies collect information that assists Aritzia to improve products and services, advertising, customer communications and the shopping experience.

For example, Aritzia may use information collected through cookies and similar technologies to recognize the user of Aritzia's websites and supplement our confidential profile for that user, determine a user's general location to tailor the website content to that user's location, track use of the websites, offer personalized web page content, information and advertisements, and otherwise facilitate and improve the website experience. You may choose to decline or disable cookies if your web browser permits, but doing so may affect your ability to access or use certain features of Aritzia's websites. Information about how Google uses cookies and how you can limit or disable certain kinds of cookies on your personal computer or mobile device is available here: [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) and [www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

Aritzia may use web beacons, pixel or gif tags, and action tags to confirm that e-mail messages have been delivered and opened. You may opt-out of receiving e-mails in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Information provided by cookies may be collected and processed by Aritzia or by its third party service providers, including Google and Facebook.

###### Do Not Track

Aritzia does not respond to do not track signals.

###### Third Party Analytics and Ad Serving Services on Aritzia’s Websites.

Aritzia uses certain third-party analytics and/or ad serving services on its websites. The providers of these services may independently collect, use, and disclose your IP address address and the general location of the IP address, together with information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites that they service in accordance with their own privacy policies (and not this privacy policy). These services may use their own cookies and other data collection technologies. They may use this information in order to improve your experience, to gain a view of how people are using websites that they service so that improvements can be made, and as otherwise permitted in their privacy policies. 

Aritzia’s websites may make use of Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Aritzia and third party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as Google Analytics cookies) and third party cookies to collect information, including but not limited to, geographic, demographic, and interest reporting information, to recognize and understand user preferences, make improvements to Aritzia’s websites and services, choose content to display to you, and for other business purposes. 

You may opt-out of tracking and prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics by visiting https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

###### Interest-Based Advertising on Third Party Websites and Online Services. 

Aritzia's websites may use cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies to store on your browser information about your use of Aritzia's websites (including items viewed, added to your shopping cart or purchased, and the Internet address of your computer) so that Aritzia's third party service providers (such as Facebook) may display advertisements likely to be of interest to you when you access other websites, social media sites or other online services.

You may opt-out of receiving interest-based advertisements on a website, social media site or other online service by using their advertising preferences settings. If you do so, you may still see Aritzia’s ads on the site but the ads will not be based tracking technologies.

Information about online interest-based advertising and how you can opt-out of receiving those ads are available here: [youradchoices.ca/choices](https://youradchoices.ca/choices), [aboutads.info/choices](https://aboutads.info/choices) and [www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/). Information about ads on Facebook is available here: [www.facebook.com/help/516147308587266/?helpref=hc_fnav.](https://www.facebook.com/help/516147308587266/?helpref=hc_fnav)

###### Social Networking and Similar Situations

When you use certain aspects of Aritzia's websites or other services, or post information to other social networking sites (e.g., there may be links to Aritzia's Facebook or Twitter pages or you may be able to "like" a product on your Facebook account or "pin" a product on your Pinterest account), the personal information that you post or share in connection with these third party sites is visible to other persons and can be read, collected, used and disclosed by other persons, including to send unsolicited messages. As will be evident, in such a case, you will be leaving Aritzia's website and going to the third party's website. Any information provided to such third party social networking sites and other sites is governed by their own privacy policies, which you may read on the applicable site. You are solely responsible for the personal information that you choose to post or share in those situations. Aritzia has no control over, or responsibility or liability for, the use, disclosure, and retention of the personal information that you disclose in those situations, and the use, disclosure, and retention of the disclosed information is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Please be careful when disclosing your personal information in those situations.

###### Disclosure of Personal Information

Affiliates — Aritzia LP and its affiliates (including Aritzia LP) may share your personal information with each other and use it in connection with our relationship with you for the provision of our products and services, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Suppliers and Service Providers — Aritzia may disclose your personal information to Aritzia's suppliers and service providers to provide products and services to Aritzia (including to provide payment processing services, Aritzia Concierge, customer communications, data processing and data management, marketing, advertising, fraud detection, address validation, and tax services), to assist Aritzia to use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (including to process your transactions and payments, fulfill your orders, deliver products to you, and provide customer service).

For example, Aritzia engages service providers to help operate Aritzia's websites, advertising, and e-mail services and to analyze information collected through the websites, advertising, and e-mail (including through cookies and other similar technologies).

Aritzia requires its suppliers and service providers to agree to use your personal information only for the purposes for which it is provided to them, and to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Others — Aritzia may disclose your personal information as required by legal disclosure obligations under applicable law, including to comply with a subpoena, warrant or court or arbitral order, or litigation disclosure obligations. Aritzia may also disclose your personal information if Aritzia reasonably believes disclosure is necessary or appropriate in connection with national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance. Aritzia may also disclose your personal information as otherwise required by law, or authorized by law in connection with a legal investigation, or if Aritzia reasonably believes the disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect and enforce Aritzia's legal rights, interests and remedies or protect the business, operations or customers of Aritzia or other persons (including detecting and preventing fraud and preventing violation of the terms of use that govern Aritzia's websites). Aritzia has no control over, or responsibility or liability for, the further use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information disclosed in those circumstances, and the further use, disclosure, and retention of the disclosed information is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

For example, Aritzia may disclose information to law enforcement authorities or other businesses and organizations in connection with the detection, prevention and prosecution of activities that Aritzia reasonably believes to be unlawful or fraudulent (including activities at Aritzia's retail stores or websites), and the disclosed information may include personal information of the individuals suspected of involvement in unlawful or fraudulent activities.

Aritzia may disclose your personal information in connection with a proposed or actual business transaction, such as a corporate reorganization, merger or acquisition, or the sale of some or all of Aritzia's business or assets (including in connection with a bankruptcy proceeding), but Aritzia will require that the information recipient agree to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

###### Retention, Location, and Protection of Personal Information

Aritzia retains your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy or such longer retention period as may be required or permitted by applicable law.

Aritzia will store and process your personal information in Canada, the United States, and other countries. The laws of other countries regarding the collection, use, disclosure, and retention of personal information may be different from the laws of Canada and the United States, and their laws may be different from the laws of your country. The disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy may result in your personal information being transferred outside of Canada, the United States, or your country.

Aritzia employs reasonable safeguards - including administrative, technical and physical measures - appropriate to the sensitivity of the personal information in its possession or under its control in order to protect that information from unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, disposal, or similar risks. While Aritzia uses reasonable efforts to protect your information, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, and therefore, Aritzia cannot guarantee absolute security of your personal information.

###### Accuracy and Access to Personal Information

You can help Aritzia maintain the accuracy and completeness of your information (including your Aritzia website account information) by notifying Aritzia of any changes to your personal information. You may update your Aritzia website account information through Aritzia's websites.

You may request access to your personal information and information about Aritzia's collection, use, disclosure, and retention of that information by sending your request to Aritzia's Chief Privacy Officer at one of the addresses noted below. Subject to applicable exceptions and limitations prescribed by law, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information, and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and to have it amended as appropriate.

###### Other Matters

Business Contact Information — To the extent permitted by law, the provisions of this Privacy Policy concerning personal information do not apply to information (such as your name, position or title, business address, business telephone number, business fax number, and business e-mail address) that enable you to be contacted at a place of business.

Personal Information of Children — Aritzia does not knowingly collect personal information from children who are under 13 years of age. Please immediately contact Aritzia's Chief Privacy Officer at one of the addresses noted below if you believe that Aritzia has unintentionally collected personal information from a child under 13 years of age. If Aritzia learns that it has inadvertently collected the personal information of a child under 13 years of age, Aritzia will use reasonable efforts to delete that information from its systems (except to the extent that retention of the personal information is required or permitted by applicable law).

Employment — Aritzia may use and disclose your personal information to administer and process your application for employment with Aritzia and related matters.

Other Websites/Online Services — Aritzia's website and online services may contain links to other websites or online services. When you use those links you are contacting another website or service. Aritzia has no responsibility or liability for, or control over, those other websites or service or their collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information. Please refer to the privacy policies and terms of use that apply to those other websites or online services.

Policy Changes — Aritzia may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on Aritzia's website at [www.aritzia.com](https://www.aritzia.com/en/home). Aritzia's collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information will be governed by the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at that time. Your continued dealings with Aritzia subsequent to any changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your consent to the collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information in accordance with the changed Privacy Policy. Accordingly, you should check the "Last updated" date of this Privacy Policy (at the bottom of the page) and review any changes since the last version.

Unsubscribing to Newsletters and Messages — You may unsubscribe from Aritzia's electronic newsletters and similar messages by using the applicable self-service unsubscribe procedure (for example, by clicking an unsubscribe link in an e-mail or adjusting your website user account preferences) or by contacting Aritzia Concierge at [service@aritzia.com](mailto:service@aritzia.com) or 1-855-ARITZIA (274-8942). From time to time, Aritzia may use your personal information to communicate with you regarding important matters, such as information about your purchases or updates to Aritzia's Privacy Policy or the terms of use that govern Aritzia's websites. Because that information is important, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

Contacting Aritzia's Chief Privacy Officer — If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact Aritzia's Chief Privacy Officer by mail, facsimile, or e-mail at: Aritzia - Chief Privacy Officer, #118 - 611 Alexander Street, Vancouver, BC, Canada V6A 1E1, facsimile no.: 604.251.6575, e-mail: [cpo@aritzia.com](mailto:cpo@aritzia.com?Subject=Aritzia%20Privacy%20Policy).

English Language — You and Aritzia have each expressly requested and required that this Privacy Policy and all other related documents be drawn up in the English language. _Les parties conviennent et exigent expressément que cette Politique et tous les documents qui s'y rapportent soient rédigés en anglais_.

Notices to You — You consent to Aritzia sending you emails (to the email addresses you provide to Aritzia) regarding this Policy and related matters.
